const Quiz = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Who's the CEO of Arsenal ? ",
    answers: ["Smith", "Hill-Wood", "Venkatesham"],
    corectAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "7 * 5 + 6 -4 -3 -11 +1 * 4 =  ? ",
    answers: ["27", "26", "28"],
    corectAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "The first  iphone was a dual mode cordless voip network phone launched by which company ? ",
    answers: ["Celtel", "Cisco", "Iphone"],
    corectAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: " How many 3's are there in the days of the month of January  ? ",
    answers: ["3", "4", "5"],
    corectAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "The most expensive spice by weight is ? ",
    answers: ["Saffron", "Cardamom", "Cinnamon"],
    corectAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Being on cloud nine means ? ",
    answers: ["very high", "very sad", "very happy"],
    corectAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "Who's the only actor to receive Oscar nominations for acting in Lord of the Rings movie ? ",
    answers: ["McKellen", "Aragon", "Gimli"],
    corectAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: " Javascript was first known as  ? ",
    answers: ["Livescript", "Mocha", "Nativescript"],
    corectAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "The spear used by the Dora Milaje army of the Wakanda people was made of ?",
    answers: ["Gibeon", "Vibranium", "Steel"],
    corectAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "When you refer to celebrity Shawn Corey you are referring to  ? ",
    answers: ["Usher", "Fetty Wap", "Jay Z"],
    corectAnswer: 2,
  },
];
export default Quiz;
